THEODORE BONHAM

Sandy, UT 84070 tedbonham99@gmail.com (206)817-9887

I am Theodore Bonham, a young and adaptable worker looking to forward my career and experiences. I have been self-teaching myself to code on and off for 4 years now, and have quite a wide variety of experiences and skills to bring with it. A drive to succeed is one of the highest priorities that I hold. I am looking for a team that I can stay with for a long time, helping both myself and the team grow and prosper.

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

WORK EXPERIENCE

Temp Agent

Express Employment Professionals - Cottonwood Heights, UT

February 2020 to Present

Assist with any client company needs, client companies listed below.

Clinical Innovations

- · Maintain a clean warehouse
- Order requests by priority, ensuring the most needed parts are available for production to use.
- Ensure pick requests are done in a timely manner, with all parts and pieces accounted for, and if parts are unavailable, ensuring everything has been done to make sure the problem is resolved quickly.
- · Process returns and reshelve units accordingly.
- Train new hires, maintaining a positive manner and workspace.
- Ensure proper paperwork and digital management has been taken care of for each order so that digital inventory reflects physical.

Instructure

- Transfer Data from outside sources to the canvas interface. Duties include:
- Altering data to fit canvas format
- · Re pathing files
- · Meeting attendance and awareness
- Keeping up to QA Standards.

Security Officer

G4S Solutions USA - West Jordan, UT November 2019 to February 2020

- Patrol Site in a timely and productive manner.
- Dress in compliance with provided attire.
- Report daily logs, and incident reports with accurate and detailed wording.
- Assist with monitoring traffic at the site.
- Provide assistance with security regulated devices (e.g. access cards).
- Be diligent at all times.
- Patrolled United Healthgroup Optum Bank
- Enforced security regulations
- · Documented reports of suspicious activity

Sales Associate

Wicked Selections - Sandy, UT January 2019 to December 2019

Assist customers with finding a good flavor of e-juice, and selling said juice. Helping customers get the new device's setup. Explain the difference between different devices to help the customer find the best fit for them. Helping customers find a good weapon, piece of jewelry, or self-defense item that best suits them. Explain the usage of CBD oil and its benefits.

Left due to store closure.

Customer Service Representative

Black Turtle Services - Sandy, UT August 2019 to October 2019

Collect calls and help customers apply for Health Insurance through the Marketplace. Answer calls related to health insurance knowledge.

Lifeguard/Water Safety Instructor

City of Lynnwood Recreation - Lynnwood, WA

February 2015 to February 2015

Duties as Water Safety Instructor

- Create and execute a plan for class activities; assist and educate students on how to swim and be safe in, on, and around water.
- Adjust class activities and plans based on age, and learning speed of the students.
- Maintain contact with parents and/or guardian on how well the student is doing in class, and encourage activities to continue improvement at home.

Duties as Lifeguard

- Maintain safety in and around the pool
- Respond to first aid emergencies in an efficient and effective manner.
- Maintain a "ten-second scan" of the pool, maintaining visual contact with appropriate sectors of the water and ensuring patrons are safe within it.
- Answer customer questions and ensure customer satisfaction.

EDUCATION

High school or equivalent

Meadowdale High School - Lynnwood, WA

September 2013 to June 2017

High School Diploma in Education

Edmonds Community College - Lynnwood, WA

SKILLS

- CUSTOMER SERVICE (5 years)
- Microsoft office (10+ years)
- Excel (6 years)
- Cash Handling (Less than 1 year)
- Data Analysis
- HTML5 (2 years)
- CSS
- JavaScript

LINKS

http://tbonham.slccwebdev.com/

https://www.teds-tree.com

CERTIFICATIONS AND LICENSES

Driver's License

July 2017 to August 2022

Washington Drivers License

ASSESSMENTS

Logic & Critical Thinking — Expert

April 2020

Using logic to solve problems.

Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/share to profile/7dd5b21821c41204ff7b20fbb7c40b96

Mechanical Knowledge — Highly Proficient

May 2020

Understanding and applying mechanical concepts and processes.

Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/share_to_profile/

9e736547e0de8ecf2e061da8b7dee733eed53dc074545cb7

Indeed Assessments provides skills tests that are not indicative of a license or certification, or continued development in any professional field.

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Skills

Computer Skils- Experienced Able to adapt quickly to new environments

Math Skills- Skillful Quick Learner

Customer Service- Highly Experienced Challenge Oriented

Sales Expereince- Well Versed Thrives in Fast Paced Environment